Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jitradaphuakkansri-0ab75a21b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
IBM SPSS Statistics
Recruiting
Research

Jitrada Phuakkansri

Talent Acquisition Specialist at LINE MAN Wongnai Bangkok City

Summary

As a Talent Acquisition Specialist at LINE MAN Wongnai. I find great people and find them great career.

My favourite parts is connecting people who have passion for working in Software Engineering and more.

I look forward to connecting with you!

Experience

LINE MAN Wongnai
Talent Acquisition Specialist
October 2019 - Present (2 years 5 months)
Bangkok City, Thailand

- Create job descriptions to attract candidates in Business & Software Development field.
- Manage candidate interviews with online scheduling software; Zoom Google Meet.
- Coordinate with hiring managers to identify staffing needs in Business & Software Development areas.
- Design social media graphics and edit post for job openings.
- Sourcing potential candidates through online channels including jobs Board and LinkedIn.
- Keep records of all materials used for recruitment, including interview notes and related paperwork, to share with key stakeholders.
- Counsel the candidate on corporate benefits, salary, and corporate environment.

Thammasat University Undergraduate Teaching Assistant April 2019 - September 2019 (6 months)

Pathum Thani, Thailand

- Responsible for developing, grading, writing assignments, quizzes and exam.
- Performed administrative and clerical work; corrected and graded exam papers & prepared progress reports of students.

- Consistently provided feedback on assignments before established deadlines.
- Participated in the assessment process using methods and techniques and provide effective, timely, and appropriate feedback to students to support their learning.

Thammasat University
Research Assistant
July 2018 - September 2018 (3 months)
Pathum Thani, Thailand

- Developed research proposal on structure/function studies of Justice in collaboration with 7-person research team.
- Conducted literature searches, helped in conducting quantitative analytical processes of data using SPSS to test.
- Followed-up with a caseload of 200 participants which included interviewing.
- Performed all required tasks to keep the interview running smoothly such as preparing document, questionnaire survey, and communication between research team and key person.

Education

Thammasat University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Sociology and Anthropology · (May 2015 - May 2019)

Satriwithaya School

High School Diploma, Arts and Math Intensive · (August 2009 - October 2015)